Previously on "Desperate Housewives"...
前情提要
- you're not taking me?
- 你不带我去么？
Dad's gonna take you.
爸爸会带你去的
Lynette's new job came with a price.
Lynette为新工作做出了牺牲
If this charge sticks, I get sent away for eight years.
如果指控成立 我就要坐八年的牢
And carlos paid for his mistakes.
Carlos为旧过错付出了代价
Are you in love with mr. Williams?
你是否爱Williams先生？
No.
不爱
I think the machine picked up on something
我想测谎仪测出了我没曾留意到的东西
that I wasn't aware of.
While bree detected feelings
察觉到不曾留心的感情
she'd never known.
You come within 10 feet of her, I will have you arrested. Now get out.
你敢靠近她10尺以内 我就让你蹲监狱 赶紧滚出去
Susan discovered something...
Zach is your son, isn't he?
Zach是的儿子 对不对
Too close to home.
"惊喜"连连
The residents of the fairview county jail
Fairview县级监狱的囚犯们
looked forward to every tuesday.
Fairview县级监狱的囚犯们 每周都盼望着星期二的到来
That was the day that Gabrielle Solis
这天是Gabrielle Solis探望丈夫的日子
came to visit her husband.
The inmates went out of their way to give her compliments
人人争先恐后慇勤示意
whether she wanted them to or not.
也不管她是否乐意
With each visit,these accolades became
她每次探访 受到的赞赏愈发...
increasingly inventive.
她每次探访 受到的赞赏愈发... 创意十足
Still, Gabrielle was not flattered.
而Gabrielle却不觉荣幸
In fact, Gabrielle started to dread this special attention.
事实上 Gabrielle开始厌烦了这种特殊关照
Until one day, when...
直到有一天...
I don't think a conjugal visitis such a ridiculous request.
我不知道配偶访问的请求荒谬在哪
With all due respect, mrs. Solis,
恕我直言 Solis太太 我们首先必须等过观察阶段 好么
let's just get throughthe discovery phase first, okay?
But I don't think I can wait that long.
我恐怕等不了那么久
I am trying to get your husband out of jail.
- 我正全力帮你丈夫出狱
Do you want me to just stop everything
你想让我停下所有的活儿
so you can have  a booty call?
就为了你们能亲热一会？
Excuse me,we are husband and wife.
你想让我停下所有的活儿 就为了你们能亲热一会？
We make love. It is a very sacred covenant.
抱歉 我们是夫妻 我们做爱 这是神圣的契约
Okay, look, all we need is 20 minutes.
- 听我说 我只需要20分钟
- I said no.
我办不到
You can't tell me no.
你必须办到
You work for me.
你想办法办到
You will make it happen.
你必须办到 你为我工作 你想办法办到
You can't force me to do anything.
你不能强迫我做任何事情 我不是你的女佣
I am not your maid or your gardener.
Whoa! Oh!
也不是你的园丁
Oh, really? And how about for this?
哦是么 那这一下呢
Ow!
噢！
You crazy bitch!
你个疯婊子
Ow!
噢！
Hey, apologize to the lady.
喂 对这位女士道歉
Big mistake, pal. I play golf with the warden.
你犯了大错了 伙计
You're gonna rot--
我可跟狱长一起打高尔夫 你可要倒...啊
You heard him. Apologize.
听见了么 道歉
I am just trying to do my job. This is all her fault!
听我说 大伙 我只是在做我的工作
If she weren't so damn horny--ow!
这都是她的不对 要不是她那么饥渴...噢！
It was at that moment it occurred to Gabrielle...
就在这一刻 Gabrielle意识到...
apologize!
道歉
This was the nicest compliment she had ever received.
她没受到过比这再好的慇勤了
Desperate Housewives 2x04 - My Heart Belongs To Daddy
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
This is Dedicated to CFT
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 七宝 少数派 校对: 少数派 时间轴: fisherchen
There was one thing all the fathers on Wisteria Lane had in common--
住在Wisteria路的父亲们有一个共同点
they could return home from a hard day's work to the family they'd left behind
劳顿一天的他们可以回到他丢下的家人们身边
and not feel at all guilty about the precious moments they had missed.
而丝毫不为没能陪伴家人而愧疚
Sadly,the same could not be said for the working mothers.
可悲的是 工作的母亲们却做不到这一点
Hey, honey, I held dinner for as long as I could.
嗨 宝贝 我把晚餐一再推迟了
It just got...
too late for them.
但后来...实在太晚了
You couldn't have given 'em coffee or something?
你就不能给他们喝点咖啡什么的？
I just feel like I'm missing out on their lives entirely.
我觉得我已经完全脱离他们的生活了
Hey, you sit, eat, and I will fill you in.
嗨 你坐下 吃饭 我来给你讲
Oh, don't eat that. That's been sitting out for hours.
哦 别吃这个 都放了好久了 这是留给Mulberry太太的
That's for mrs. Mulberry.
This...
哦 别吃这个 都放了好久了 这是留给Mulberry太太的
is for you.
这个 是给你的
Oh, mrs. Mulberry.
- 哦 Mulberry太太
Parker has an imaginary friend.
哦 Mulberry太太 Parker幻想他有这么个朋友
Um, british nanny.
英国保姆
I think he really locked into the whole "Mary Poppins" thing.
我想他对《欢乐满人间》太着迷了
Is that why he's sleeping with an umbrella?
- 他就为这个抱着雨伞睡觉？
He carries it with him everywhere.
他走到哪都带着
It's a security blanket.
让他有安全感
When did this start?
什么时候开始的？
About a week ago, I guess.
大概一周以前吧
And you don't find it odd that Parker's new nanny
Parker的新保姆正好在我开始工作时后出现
made her appearance right at the time I went back to work?
你不觉得奇怪么
Kids have imaginary friends.
小孩都有想像的朋友
It's no big deal.
没什么大不了的
I'll agree with you to a point,
我也同意你
when they're flying kangaroos or giant robots,
要是那些朋友是会飞的袋鼠 巨型机器人的话
not surrogate mommies.
但这个等于代理母亲
Hey...
Parker is having a little trouble adjusting.
parker只是还不适应
That's all.
不过如此
Apparently, so are you.
你也是呀
Honey, don't be so sensitive.
- 宝贝 别这么敏感
I hope you're right.
- 希望你是对的
At the risk of sounding too sensitive,
我不想听起来很敏感
how come she gets a bigger portion?
但为什么她那份比我的多？
That's it?
这就走了？
You're the one who said you wanted things to be casual between us.
是你说你要我们慢慢来的
but that doesn't mean we have to act like brother and sister.
对 但我们不用搞得好像兄妹似的
I mean, you bought me ribs. I have gratitude to express.
你给我买了排骨 我要表示一下
I can't do this.
- 怎么了？
This casual thing--
- 我做不来 什么“慢慢来”
it's--it's weird.
感觉很怪
No! No! It's not.
不 不 不怪阿
We're just gonna pretend like it was when we first started dating.
我们就假装好像刚开始交往
We just see each other occasionally,
偶尔见见面
you know, until we get the zach thing resolved.
直到我们把Zach这件事解决了
Yeah, well, we'll just be easy about it. No commitments.
对 就放轻松点
Except, of course,
不要承诺
neither of us is allowed to date anybody else.
只是..当然了 我们不许约别人
Look, I...
听我说
I know how you feel about Zach.
我知道你对zach怎么想
And, look,
而且
I don't blame you.
我不怪你
But he's part of the package right now,
但他跟我现在“捆”在一条绳上
and either you can accept that or you can't.
你要么接受要么不接受
Well, anyway...
好了 总之...
Mike, wait!
Mike 等等
I accept.
我接受
Zach's your son.
Zach是你的儿子
And I have Julie,
我也有Julie
and you've totally accepted her.
你完全接受了她
I mean, granted, she's been the model child so far.
纵然 她目前是个模范儿童
But she's almost 15. She's going to turn on me any minute.
但她快15岁了 随时都会跟我对着干
And you better be there to help me when it gets ugly.
而我跟她闹翻的时候你最好在身边帮我
I will.
我会的
Good night.
晚安
- Uh, Susan? - Yeah?
Susan?
Technically, we don't have to be casual anymore.
理论上说 我们不用再慢慢来了
I can be naked in 20 seconds.
我20秒就可以脱光 边跑边脱
That includes travel time.
Carlos, will you calm down?
Carlos 你冷静点
You incited a prison riot.
你引发了监狱暴动
It wasn't a riot.
- 那不算暴动
It was more of a melee.
一起斗殴而已
Who's going to defend me now?
- 现在谁给我辩护？
Doyle knew my case.
Doyle了解我的案子
- He knew the judge.
他认识法官
He called me a bitch.
他叫我婊子！
Well, were you acting like one?
那你是不是表现成那样了？
He refused to help me get a conjugal visit.
他拒绝帮忙申请配偶探访
My lawyer's in traction because you wanted sex?
我的律师现在不愿意就因为你要做爱？
Not just for me, for us.
不光是为了我 为了我们俩
In case you haven't noticed, Carlos,
给你提个醒 Carlos
our marriage is still on shaky ground.
我们的婚姻还处在不稳固阶段
And you thought a conjugal visit would fix it?
一次配偶探访就能解决了？
It couldn't hurt.
总没坏处啊
Ever since you've been in here, all we do is bicker.
自从你进监狱以后 我们除了吵架没干别的
That's all we ever did when I was out. That's what we do!
我没进监狱时候我们也是这样 我们就是这样！
Yeah, but when we would finish arguing,
是啊 但每次吵完了
we would have this great sex. Now all we do is fight,
我们就会翻云覆雨 现在只剩下吵架了
and there's no payoff, and it sucks!
没有回报 糟糕透了!
You and I need to get laid!
我想要跟你干！
Oh, don't judge me.
看什么看！
You're not in here because you got caught helping the poor.
你们谁也不是因为帮助穷人被关起来的
See, we'd be enjoying this argument more
明白吗 我们要是有盼头 吵得也会开心点了
if we had something to look forward to.
Fine. Get the damn lawyer.
好! 把该死的律师找来
And make it quick.
尽量快点
I take it that was my good night kiss.
我就把这当成晚安之吻了
George, you're a very special friend.
George 你对我来说很特别 真的
You are, but Rex hasn't been dead four weeks,
但Rex过世还不到四周
so I think kissing on the lips is--
所以我想接吻不是...
Exactly.
- 非常妥当
I hope you don't mind.
说得对 希望你不介意
Andrew, what are you doing?
- Andrew 你干什么呢？
Taking out the garbage.
扔垃圾
Of course. You remember mr. Williams.
是啊 你还记得Williams先生吧？
Hi, Andrew.
- 嗨 Andrew
George.
- George
Uh, well, it's getting late, so...
这么晚了 那...
yeah. So let me know if you want to go out to dinner again soon.
对 要是你哪天想出去吃饭就告诉我
There's a couple new restaurants I'd like to try.
最近有几家新饭店开张 我想试试
You know, we've been eating out a lot lately.
咱们最近总出去吃饭 不如你周五来吃个便饭 不是很好么？
Why don't you come over friday for a home-cooked meal?
- Wouldn't that be nice? - Oh, I would love that.
哦 再好不过了
So you leaving or what?
- 你还不走？
We're not done talking.
我们还没聊完呢
She said it was getting late.
她说天已经晚了
In case you missed that, that was a hint.
提醒你一下 那是个暗示
Andrew...
Andrew
that wasn't a hint.
我没暗示什么
I'll go when I'm ready.
我想走的时候就走
Actually, it is getting late, and I am tired so...
其实是有点晚了 我有点累了..
see? You heard the lady. Now...
怎么样 听见女士的话了 现在走吧
take off.
Andrew.
怎么样 听见女士的话了 现在走吧
It's okay. He's not really that tough.
没事 他没多强
He knows I would never hit a child.
他知道我不打孩子的
Andrew!
Andrew
George!
Andrew George!
Stop it, the two of you, this instant!
住手 你们两个 马上！
This was a perfectly lovely evening,
这本来是个美好的夜晚 现在被你们俩给毁了
and now the both of you have ruined it.
I will not tolerate this kind of behavior.
我不能容忍这种行为 听明白了么
Do you understand?
George, we'll see you friday for dinner.
George 周五晚餐时见
I'll be serving fish.
我会做鱼
Hey, wake up, sleepyhead. Parker.
嗨 起来了 瞌睡虫
Hi. Hi ya, pal.
Parker 嗨 早啊 小家伙
Hey, what do you say
you and me go get some donuts, okay,
咱们一起去买点甜甜圈怎么样
before mommy has to go to work?
咱们一起去买点甜甜圈怎么样 在妈妈上班之前？
Yeah? Come on.Come on. Come on. Come on.
在妈妈上班之前？
All right. Oh.
起来 起来 起来 起来 好啦
So what do you think you're gonna have,huh? Jelly?
你想吃点什么呢 果冻？
Stop!
- 停车
I forgot mrs. Mulberry.
- 我忘了Mulberry太太了
What?
什么？
Oh, um, well, since I'm here,
哦 既然我在这了
maybe she could just relax in the house for a while,okay?
也许她不如就在家休息一会 怎么样？
No, I need her!
不行 我就要她
Okay.
好吧
Hello, mrs. Mulberry.
哈喽 Mulberry太太
Don't forget to buckle up.
别忘记安全带
Here we go.
出发了
Wait!
等一下
You forgot her umbrella.
你忘拿她的伞了
Well, Parker, we don't have time.
- Parker我们没时间了
No!
不行
she needs it.
她需要伞
Hey, what are you still doing here?
嗨 你怎么还在这呢？
I'm looking for Parker's umbrella.
我在找Parker的伞
Have you seen it?
你看见了么？
No. Nope. Sorry.
没 没看见 不好意思
Hey, honey, you better hurry.
宝贝 你最好快点
You're gonna be late for work.
你要上班迟到了
Thank you for that.
谢谢提醒
so I brought her sun hat instead,
我找不到Mulberry的伞 所以我把她的太阳帽带来了 行么
And here we go.
- 我们出发
It's in the shower.
在浴室呢
What?
什么
Mrs. Mulberry says she left it in the shower.
Mulberry说她把伞放在浴室了
Well, why didn't mrs. Mulberry
为什么Mulberry在我把你房间翻的底朝天之前
looking for it, hmm?
不主动提供这个信息呢 嗯？
No, I'm not gonna get the damn umbrella!
不去！我不拿那把该死的破伞！
I'm so sorry, sweetie. I am not mad at you.
对不起 宝贝 我没对你发火
What are you doing?
你干什么？
we don't want donuts.
我们不想吃甜甜圈
Andrew, you are not leaving the house dressed like that.
你不能穿成这样就出门
I'm just going to meet some of the guys at the swim club.
我就是去找几个哥们去游泳俱乐部
I don't care. Put this on.
我不管 把这个穿上
and the least you can do is not humiliate us.
你出了这个门 就就代表我们家 最起码的不要让我们蒙羞
Yes, a bad one.
对 很坏的样子
I hope you haven't made plans for tomorrow night.
我希望你明晚没有安排
Look, if you think I'm having dinner
你要是以为我会和那个卖药的吃饭 那你就是疯了
with the pharmacist, you're crazy.
Part of the reason I'm having him over
我请他来的部分原因就是为了让你认识他
is so that you can get to know him.
Yeah, well, I don't want to get to know him.
是啊 我不想认识他
Your feelings are perfectly normal.
宝贝 你现在的感觉再正常不过
But George isn't trying to take your father's place.
但是George并没有要代替你父亲的位置
He's--well, he's just a friend.
- 他..他只是个朋友
Really? Just a friend?
真的么 只是朋友？
So you're not planning on getting more serious
那你没有打算和他以后认真发展？
with this guy in the future?
You know, I haven't even thought about it.
我连想都没想过
You're worried about a ripped t-shirt
你担心一件破掉的T恤
humiliating this family?
会有辱家门?
Wait till people see that you're dating the town nerd
等着看人们知道你在丈夫葬礼不到一个月 就和镇上的呆子约会会怎么说吧
less than a month after your husband's funeral.
I'm sorry, but I already have plans.
- 抱歉 我已经有安排了
Andrew, don't you have a meet at the swim club?
- Andrew 你不是在游泳俱乐部有活动吗？
Yeah, so?
对阿 怎么了
Doesn't it require a large entrance fee,
它不是需要很贵的入场费吗？
one that you can't afford by yourself?
你自己支付不起吧
Are you blackmailing me into coming to dinner?
你在威胁我参加晚餐吗？
Oh, you don't know the lengths I'd go to for even seating.
哦 你可不知道即使为了一个座位我都会不择手段
Mayer, is this yours?
Mayer 这是你的吗？
Blew into my front yard.
Oh,sorry. I'm helping Mike find Zach.
哦 对不起 我在帮Mike找Zach
You know, so we can all rest easy at night.
你知道 这样晚上才能睡得安稳点
Uh-huh. And put him in jail?
嗯 把他送进监狱吗?
I don't think Mike
我想Mike
would do that to his own son.
不会对亲生儿子这么做
That Mike's Zach'sreal father?
- Mike是Zach的生父？
Yes.
我知道
Oh. Julie told Karl, Karl told me,
哦 Julie告诉了Karl Karl告诉了我
and I, well, sent out a few e-mails.
然后我 发了几封电邮
Well,thanks for your discretion.
感激你这么慎重
Boy, you would do anything to get Mike Delfino to love you.
真是 你为了让mike delfino爱你什么都干
So what's gonna happen to little creepy when he gets here?
等那个小恐怖分子来了你们要怎么办?
Are you gonna be tucking him in at night?
晚上给他盖被子？
Making him breakfast in the morning?
早上给他做早餐？
Careful to bob and weave as he tries to blow your head off?
他要把你一枪爆头时候左躲右闪？
You know, Edie, could you just back off?
Edie 你能离我远点呢 ？
I mean, the truth is, we're probably never gonna find Zach anyway.
事实上 我们可能永远也找不到Zach
It's a needle in a haystack.
这是海底捞针
Oh, I see.
哦 明白了
And then you'll still come off as little miss perfect, self-sacrificing girlfriend,
这样你就仍然是那个 “十全十美自我牺牲女友”小姐
putting his needs
把他的需要
ahead of yours.
放在自己的需要之前
Oh, why you conniving little shrew.
哦 天 你这小泼妇 颇有心机嘛
I don't know why we're not closer.
真不知道我们怎么会合不来的
There was a reason David Bradley
david bradle成为镇上最成功律师是有原因的
was the most successful lawyer in all of fairview.
His arguments were persuasive...
他有惊人的说服力
no one ever has to know.
我跟谁也不会说的
His manner was forceful...
他的行动力度十足
take it off. Take it off.
脱了 脱了
And he tended to win on appeal.
他的诉请总被接受
Please.
他的诉请总被接受 求求你...
And when it came to the more challenging cases,
而当有更富挑战性的案子时
he knew it was to his advantage
他知道一开始就拒绝绝对是优势
to raise the first objection.
I'm not gonna take your case.
- 我不接受你的案子
What?
- 什么？
yes.
什么事？
sorry to interrupt, mr. Bradley.
抱歉打扰 Bradley先生
Your dinner just canceled. Want me to pull the reservation?
- 你的晚餐取消了 需要我放弃预约么
No, I still have to eat. I'm sorry, where were we?
不 我还是要吃饭的
You were about to turn me down, and then you reconsidered
- 你刚正打算回绝我
once you realized I was gonna throw a ton of money at you,
然后你想到我会给你砸大笔的钱
which I am.
我也是这么打算的
Ah. It's not about the money for me anymore, mrs. Solis.
阿 对我来说不是钱的问题 Solis太太
The fact is, if I don't feel passionately about a client,
实际上 如果我对一个客户没有热情 如果我的胸中没感到火一般灼烧
if I don't feel that fire in my belly,
如果我的胸中没感到火一般灼烧
I don't bring my a-game to court,
我没法在法庭上有一等表现
and from what I've read, it'll take my a-game to save your husband.
我需要有一等表现才能救你丈夫
Is this about the gay bashing thing?
是关于他殴打同志的事么
He's innocent.
他是清白的
He went berserk and attacked a man in court.
他法庭上暴怒袭击了别人
Yeah, but that was a jealousy thing.
- 是啊 那是因为嫉妒
The man that my husband was trying to kill in court
我丈夫在庭上企图宰了的人
is not the least bit gay, trust me.
一丁点的同志倾向都没有 相信我吧
Your file also says you're seeking conjugal visits.
你的资料上说你在申请配偶访问
Trying to keep the old marriage alive, huh?
想要让婚姻死灰复燃是吧？
Why does everybody have a problem with me having sex with my husband?
我要和丈夫做爱怎么每个人都有意见
Can I be frank?
我能说实话吗？
Only if it ends with me getting what I want.
- 只要你能让我得到我想要的
Your marriage is doomed.
你的婚姻完蛋了
I've been doing this for a long time, mrs. Solis.
我做这行已经很久了 Solis太太
I know what incarceration can do to a relationship.
我知道牢狱会怎样影响婚姻
but when you throw incement walls,
当你被扔进水泥墙内
armed guards, iron bars,
狱警前 铁栏后
it tends to go down hill rather quickly.
婚姻状况就会急转直下
Conjugal visits not with standing.
配偶访问帮不上忙
listen, you want my advice?
听我说 想听我的意见吗？
Walk away.
走人吧
You're young.
你还年轻
You made a mistake. You learn from it.
你犯了错 吸取教训
Maybe next time you'll marry smarter.
也许下次你选丈夫就更明智些
Now if you'll excuse me, I have dinner reservations.
不要意思 我有几个晚餐预约
Reservation.
只有一个
You're eating alone, remember?
你一个人吃饭 记得么
And I have a feeling it's not the first time.
我猜想这也不是你第一次一个人吃了
I'm so sorry I couldn't get here sooner.
真对不起 我来晚了
I forgot my husband had to take our youngest
我忘了我丈夫要带我家老么去看儿科
to the pediatrician and...
it's all right, mrs. Scavo.
没关系 Scavo太太
So...what did Parker do?
那么..Parker干了什么了
Are you aware that your son has an imaginary friend,
你知道你的儿子有幻想的朋友吗？
a mrs. Mulberry?
Mulberry太太
Yes. We've met.
是的 我们见过面 呵
Parker demanded that
昨天 美术课上Parker要求我们 给Mulberry太太一个画架
mrs. Mulberry get her own easel during art, which was fine.
给Mulberry太太一个画架，我们答应了
But today it was a desk.
但今天他又要求一张桌子
And unfortunately, we didn't have an extra desk.
但不幸的是 我们没有多余的桌子
Oh.
噢
That must have been ugly.
- 哦 那情况肯定糟透了
It was.
的确
Patty was rammed
Patty被戳到了
with this.
被这个
Oh. I am so sorry.
哦 真对不起
Mrs. Scavo,
Scavo太太
have you experienced a death in your family recently?
- 最近家里有人过世吗？
No. No. Why?
没 没有 怎么了
Imaginary friends are often created as a coping mechanism
想像朋友多半是为了弥补他们失去的东西而产生的
to--to deal with loss.
Or it might occur as the result of some major change
或者也可能是因为生活上某些突变
or extensive alteration in their lives.
A manifestation of some deep-seated unhappiness.
正是如此 是心底深层悲伤的表现
Can you think of anything
that might shed a little bit of light
你能想到什么原因能解释他的行为吗？
on this for us?
Mrs. Scavo?
Scavo太太
thank you.
谢谢
And I'm thinking, it's the golden gate bridge.
我在想 就是金门桥 在那拍日落多么合适阿
What a great place to get a picture of the sunset.
So I lean out way over the rail to get the shot.
我就把身子探出去去照相
Next thing I know, the police arrive.
过一会儿 警察来了 有人用手机打了911
People had called 9-1-1 from their cell phones.
Thought I was suicidal.
以为我要自杀呢
I can't believe how well those two are getting along.
真不敢相信他们俩能相处这么好
Yeah, it's freaky.
是啊 怪怪的
Andrew is being polite and engaging.
Andrew那么礼貌顺从
He's even laughing at george's jokes.
- 他听了George的笑话还笑呢
That's why it's freaky.
就怪在这呢
George's jokes aren't funny.
George的笑话根本不逗
so, George, can I ask you a question?
George 能问个问题吗？
And it's kind of personal.
Sure.
- 没问题
Have you ever actually been with a woman?
- 你真的和女人好过吗？
Excuse me?
- 什么？
Well, let's be honest. I think it's obvious
咱们实话实说吧
by the way that you talk and act
很明显从你的言谈举止能看出来
that you're not a player,
你不是个猛男
so I was just curious to find out
所以我很好奇
if you had ever actually gotten in the game.
你到底有没有真的“那什么”过
My experience with women is none of your business.
- 我跟女人的经历不关你的事儿
Oh, I think it is.
我想关我的事
I mean, you're dating my mom.
我想关我的事 我是说 你在跟我妈交往
dating's a little more than just holding hands.
咱们都清楚 你这个年纪 交往不会只是牵牵手
We're not dating exactly.
- 我们并不是真正意义的交往
Oh, sure you are.
哦 你们当然是
And you know what? I think it's great.
而且我觉得挺好的
But I wanna make sure my mom's happy,
但我想确保我妈妈是幸福的
you know, and it would really set my mind at ease
要是我能确信她在和懂得满足女人的人在一起 我就放心了
to know that she's with a guy that knows how to please a lady.
This is inappropriate.
这不太恰当吧
You know, my parents had a great sex life.
你知道 我父母的性生活棒极了
Man, I heard 'em through the wall of my bedroom once.
天 我隔着我卧室的墙都能听到
Please shut up.
住口
You should've heard my mom, too.
- 你真该也听听我妈妈
She had this--this weird moan.
她有一种奇怪的呻吟声
It was kind of like, um... mmm.
有点像...
Isn't that bizarre?
很怪 不是吗？
That's the sound my mom makes
这就是我妈到高潮的声音
when she climaxes.
Okay. Time for cobbler.
好了 点心时间
Sorry, one of the dessert plates doesn't match.
对不起 有一个甜品碟不搭配了
I tried to replace it, but it's spode florence.
本来想换掉 但它是spode florence的 图案很稀有
It's a rare pattern.
图案很稀有 是我外婆留下的
But hopefully once you taste the dessert,
但愿你们一尝到甜品就能忘了这个
you'll forget all about it.
George, you have to have this. It's absolutely scrumptious.
George 你必须尝尝 这简直棒透了
Mmm.
嗯...
Mmm!
Thats it.
口型:就是这个声音
go to your room!
回你的房间
You heard me. Go to your room.
听见了吗 回你房间
Mr. Williams, what's wrong?
Williams先生 怎么了？ 我说错什么话了吗？
Did I say something wrong?
我说错什么话了吗？
Bree, please back me up.
Bree 你能替我说句话吗？
I can't say. It's too sordid. But he said it!
我不能说 太下流了 但他说了
Are you gonna back me up or what?
你是不是站在我这边的？
George, I can't allow you to discipline my child
George 我不能允许你训斥我的孩子
if you won't even tell me what he did.
除非你告诉我他干了什么了
George.
George
George!
George！
mrs. Solis, David Bradley.
Solis夫人 我是David Bradley
Look, I feel really bad about the tone of our meeting,
上次我的态度不好 实在抱歉
so to make up for it, I'm gonna do you a favor.
为了表示歉意 我想帮忙
The more I think of it,
我又仔细想了想
the more I'm convinced your marriage is a train wreck--
觉得你们的婚姻基本上就好比一次火车出轨事故
the gnarly type,you know,mass casualties.
最严重的那种 死伤严重
Anyway, I'm passing on the name
不过我这有个不错的律师
of a great divorce lawyer, kir--
专门处理离婚案件 叫Kir
leaving that message on my machine.
你竟然敢留言说那样的话？！
You realize this is entirely inappropriate?
你就这么进来很没礼貌
I will tell you what is inappropriate.
- 我来告诉你什么叫没礼貌
You making sweeping assumptions about the state of my marriage.
你自以为是好像很了解我的婚姻状况
Care for a drink?
- 要喝点吗？
No!
- 不！
I like to keep a clear head when I'm telling people off.
我发火的时候要保持头脑清醒
What makes you think you know anything about me or my husband?
你凭什么对我和我丈夫指指点点？
Well, your husband's record speaks for itself.
你丈夫的案底就能说明一切
With you, I had to rely on my instincts.
至于你 我是凭直觉猜的
Would those be the same instincts
你丈夫的案底就能说明一切 至于你 我是凭直觉猜的
that picked out that cologne?
你也是凭直觉抹了这种古龙香水？
You're privileged. You're pampered.
你被惯坏了 宠坏了
You're spoiled.
You want what you want when you want it.
你随心所欲惯了
You want excitement.
你随心所欲惯了 你需要激情
A quickie every five months in a prison trailer
你需要激情 每五个月跑一趟监狱可没法满足你
isn't gonna scratch that itch.
每五个月跑一趟监狱可没法满足你
With all due respect, I will decide for myself
每五个月跑一趟监狱可没法满足你 恕我直言 我自己会决定什么能满足我
what needs to be scratched and when.
恕我直言 我自己会决定什么能满足我
Mrs. Solis, you are a beautiful,
恕我直言 我自己会决定什么能满足我 Solis夫人 你是位漂亮而让人向往的女人
desirable woman.
Solis夫人 你是位漂亮而让人向往的女人
Now your husband is a dimwit,
Solis夫人 你是位漂亮而让人向往的女人 而你丈夫则是个有暴力倾向的罪犯
corrupt, violent criminal.
而你丈夫则是个有暴力倾向的罪犯
You could do...so much better.
你能做的更好
Are you hitting on me?
What would you say if I were?
你是不是在泡我？
I'd say I'm pregnant.
-  我会说我怀孕了
So I see, you're stuck.
- 我明白了，你进退两难
I'm not stuck, mr. Bradley.
- 我不是进退两难 Bradley先生
Believe it or not, I love my husband.
信不信由你 我爱我的丈夫
I charge $700 an hour,
我每小时收费700元
plus xeroxing.
复印费另算
and I expect a conjugal visit tomorrow by noon.
我给你600 明天中午 你必须给我配偶探访权利
Aren't you demanding?
你要求可真高
Like you said...
真如你所说
I want what I want when I want it.
我随心所欲惯了
said a lot of runaways hang out here.
社会保障部门的一个女的告诉我 这个地方经常有离家出走的人出没
Just happy to be spending the day with you.
- 能和你在一起感到高兴
At homeless shelters and bus stations?
在收容所和车站也高兴？
I think we'll cover more ground if we split up.
- 分开来问快一点
Okay.
好的
Have you seen this boy?
你见过他吗？
Uh, missing kid. Anyone?
失踪儿童 有人见过吗？
Going once...
一次
going twice?
两次
keeping them and passing them out when people get their ice cream?
你能不能留着这些传单 别人来买冰淇淋的时候顺便散一下？
Huh.
嗯哼
Well, isn't that him, over there?
- 怎么了？ 那不就是他嘛？
Zach! Zach!
Zach！ Zach！
Oh, no, no, no, no.
别跑 别跑 别跑 别跑
No, no, no, no.
Don't, don't, don't, don't. Zach!
别跑 别跑 别跑 别跑
Don't, don't. Zach, don't run away!
别跑 别跑 Zach 别跑 别跑
Wait! Come on!
等一下 别跑 别跑
Just--would you get back here?!
等一下 别跑 别跑 你给我回来！
Come on, really! Let's just talk!
你给我回来！ 别跑 别跑 我们就聊聊
Damn it, Zach!
该死 zach！
It's enough already.
Aah! Oh!
别折腾了！
But there's a halfway house
没人见过zach 不过西边有家康复医院
on the west side I want to check... out.
我想去看看
I got you some ice cream.
我给你买冰淇淋了
You did?
买了？
But then I got hungry.
不过我太饿了
So then I just threw my ice cream at him and ran.
然后我就扔掉冰淇淋拚命跑
Say something
- 说句话呀
Thank god you were in flats.
还好你当时穿的是平底鞋
I'm still recovering from Mike is Zach's real father.
我还震惊于Mike竟然是zach的生父 没缓过神来
I should've told Mike I saw zach.
我应该告诉Mike我看见zach了
I'm a horrible person, right?
我这人是不是很讨厌？
Oh, Susan, come on.
susan别这么说
Zach attacked Felicia. He blew up your kitchen.
Zach袭击了Felicia 还打坏了你家厨房
Evidently, he tried to kill Mike.
他摆明了要杀死mike
I think we can all agree this kid's a freak.
我想我们大家都觉得这个孩子怪怪的
What do you think, bree?
你怎么看 bree？
it's perfectly justified that you'd be frightened of Zach.
我觉得考虑到目前的事态 你害怕Zach也是人之常情
but Zach is Mary Alice's son.
不过zach是mary alice的儿子
He grew up playing in our yards.
他是在大家院子里玩耍长大的
If he has any hope of surviving,
如果他想继续活下去的话
I have to believe he's better off here than on the streets.
在大街上流浪总比在这要好
how much going back to work would upset Parker.
我没想到我回去工作 对parker的影响会那么大
Look, he's going to be fine. He's just gotta get used
没事的 也许他现在习惯了父爱了
to daddy providing all the love.
I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
开玩笑 开玩笑
I am kidding.
开玩笑
Look, kids are resilient. He will adapt.
孩子都这样 慢慢适应就好了
Tom, he attacked a teacher with an umbrella.
- Tom 他今天拿伞打老师
It was a poke. He poked her.
不是打 戳了下而已
I don't know.
我也犯迷糊了
Maybe I shouldn't be working.
也许我不该工作
The kids would certainly benefit
父母都在家陪着当然是好事了
from having two stay-at-home parents,
although buying food might become an issue.
不过买吃的可能会成问题
Maybe I could change my work schedule,
我应该改改日程安排 多捞点空闲时间
try and get some flex time.
Would nina go for that?
- Nina会同意吗？
No. No.
不 不 不
No,no,no!
It would help if you came up with some ideas.
要不你出点主意吧？
How about hugs?
- 拥抱如何？
Yeah, I read in one of those family magazines
我看家庭杂志上说孩子
the kids are supposed to get, like, ten hugs a day.
每天至少应该被抱上10次
It makes 'em feel more secure.
说是能让他们感到安全
I say pile on the hugs.
所以我们就去多抱抱孩子
Yeah. Come here.
- 当然 来
come here.
过来
It's working, isn't it?
- 是不是很有效?
Shut up.
别说话
Hey, buddy, you busy?
嘿 小家伙 忙呢？
Yes. Mrs. Mulberry's reading to me.
恩 Mulberry夫人在给我讲故事呢
Well, isn't she nice?
她可真好
But it's time for bed, so I'm gonna tuck you in, okay?
不过现在得睡觉了 我来帮你盖被子
I'll take that.
- 我来拿 ！
No!
不要！
I know things have been hard for you
我知道自从我工作了后
since I started back to work,
你就一直不开心
but it is just as hard for me to be away from you.
不过妈妈身边没了你
And you just have to remember
妈妈我也不开心呀
that even when I'm not around,
你记住就算妈妈不在身边
my love for you is real.
我对你的爱也是真真切切的
You may not be able to see it,
你也许看不到
but it's not imaginary like mrs. Mulberry.
但绝不是想像的Mulberry夫人
It's real.
是真实的
Okay, honey?
- 这么说可以了吗 宝贝?
Mrs. Mulberry is real,
Mulberry夫人就是真的
and she said you're a liar.
她还说你撒谎骗人
Parker.
Parker
- Parker
We're reading.
我们在看书
I don't understand.
我不太明白
Why can't we see each other anymore?
为什么我们不能再见面了？
Because ever since I found out what Andrew said to you,
因为自从我知道Andrew对你说的话后
I've been doing some soul searching,
我也好好想了想
and I realize that everything's that happened
我才意识到所有的一切都是因我而起
is completely my fault.
No,no,no,
-不不不
that's ridiculous.
- 才不是呢 太荒唐了
No, it's not.
不是
All the things that Andrew's been saying
andrew的所言所为
and the way he's been acting,
it's all connected to his father's death.
都是因为他父亲去世导致的
that I need to spend more time focusing on him and his needs.
我现在明白我必须多陪陪他 了解他的想法
You know...
不错
you're right. You do need to focus on Andrew.
你说的对 你的确要多关心关心andrew
Thank you, George, for being so understanding.
- 谢谢你能理解我George
Of course.
应该的
So have you thought about counseling?
你有没有考虑过心理辅导？
That place you sent him to--
你送他去的那个--
that behavioral modification camp--
行为改变营--
he got counseling there,right?
他在那接受的辅导吧
because his behavior at the time was so completely out of bounds.
但是那时是因为他行为过分才送他去那的
You don't think that what he said to me was out of bounds?
你不觉得他对我说的话是过分行为？
I just think if I spent a lot of time with him, it'll really help.
我只是觉得多花点时间陪陪他有好处
Why not do both?
干吗不一举两得呢？ 让他和专家待上几个月然后再接回家
Let him spend a few months with some caring professionals,
You know, what he said to you was horribly rude,
我也知道他说的话是很过分 但还不至于送他去那个地方吧
but that camp, it's extreme,
and, I mean, unless I felt like Andrew was getting
除非我觉得Andrew实在无法无天了 才能...
really out of control,then...
well, let's hope it doesn't come to that.
那就希望最好别发生这种事
You know, in spite of everything that's happened,
虽然发生不愉快的事
I really like Andrew.
我还是很喜欢andrew的
Oh, George, really?
- George 真的？
Yeah. The truth is...
是的 因为...
he reminds me of me.
他让我想起年轻时候的我
The conjugal visit rules are you got 45 minutes.
规定探访时间为45分钟
We call every 15 minutes to make sure you're still here.
每15分钟我们会打电话一次确保你们人还在
You understand?
- 明白了吗？
Yes, we got it.
- 明白了
Uh,we interrupt our love making to answer the phone,
中途停下来接你们电话不然你们就放狗咬人 是吧？
or you call out the dogs.Okay!
I'm ready whenever you...
我这就好 一旦你...
obviously are.
早准备好了
Carlos, are we gonna make it?
Carlos 我们还能撑的下去吗？
We just did. You want to go again?
我们不是刚做过吗？ 你还想再做一次？
No, I'm talking about us--
不是 我是在说我们俩
our relationship, our marriage.
我们的关系 我们的婚姻
Carlos, you're going to be a father.
Carlos 你就要当爸爸了
And when you get outta here, you're gonna need to get a job
你出狱后 你得找份工作
and make an honest living for me and our child.
赚钱养我和孩子
Babe, I've learned my lesson.
心肝 我会吸取教训的
Okay, when I get out of here, everything's gonna be different.
我出去后 一切都会不同的
We're going to start over with a new life and a great family,
我们可以重新开始 好好过日子
and nothing is going to get in the way of that.
没有任何东西能阻碍我们
Hey, so you never told me--
你还没和我说呢
how's the new lawyer? You like him?
我们的新律师如何？满意吗？
yeah.
是 我还在
Yeah, I'm still here.
Okay, enough chitchat. We only have 30 minutes left,
别说废话了 还有30分钟
and I want to make the most of it.
这次我可要好好享受
Okay,please--please don't run.
别 别跑
I can't. I hurt my foot.
我跑不了 脚伤着了
I landed on it funny when I was running away from you.
上次逃跑时扭伤了
What do you want?
- 你想干吗？
To talk to you.
- 和你聊聊
Why?
- 为什么？
'Cause I havea lot of things to say.
因为我有很多话要说
So you can just listen. I'll buy you some food.
你尽管听便是了 我给你买点吃的
When was the last time you ate?
你上次吃东西是什么时候？
My dad's alive? Where is he?
我爸爸还活着？人在哪？
I don't know. He disappeared.
我不知道 失踪了
But Mike did not kill him. I mean, he's alive, you swear?
但是Mike没杀他 他还活着 你说真的？
I swear.
- 我发誓
Maybe he's in utah.
也许在犹他
I know that he used to have a life there--
我听说我出生以前他住在那
before me.
I don't know. I just--I just--
我也不知道 我得讨点钱去找他
I need to get some money and find him.
我也不知道 我得讨点钱去找他 Zach 你听我说
Zach, you know what I think?
Zach 你听我说
- I think you should come back with me.
- 我觉得你应该跟我回去
Why?
为什么？
Because there are still people at home that care about you.
因为那里还有关心你的人 还有些事你必须知道
And there's things that you need to know.
Like what?
- 什么事？
Well, I can't tell you.
我不能说
You know,you messed up a lot of people's lives, Zach.
你打扰了很多人的生活 zach 你可不能一走了之
You can't run away from that.
Do you mean Julie?
- 你是说julie？
What?
什么？
I know that I messed up her life,
我知道我闯入了她的生活 但我不是故意的
but I didn't mean to.
I really miss her out here.
我很想她
I think about her all the time.
一直都想她
Yeah, well, Julie is a really special girl.
- Julie的确是个很特别的女孩子
Has she said anything about me?
- 她有没有提起过我？
Because if she has, then I might still have a chance with her.
因为如果她提过我 说明我们还有机会在一起
If I come back with you,
如果我跟你回去
then I-I could make it up to her.
就能弥补过去了
Do you know what I think?
我是这么想的
I think you were right.
我想你是对的
I think you should try to find your father first.
你应该先去找你父亲
- Yeah?
- 真的？
Yeah.
真的
I mean, now that you know he's okay,
竟然你知道他还活着 就应该去找他
you should go to him.
He'll want to take care of you.
他会照顾你的 父母的天职嘛
That's what parents do.
父母的天职嘛
Let me help.
我可以帮忙
How much money do you think you'll need to get to utah?
你去犹他要多少钱？
Daddy, I can't find mrs. Mulberry's umbrella.
爸爸 我找不到Mulberry夫人的阳伞了
Where is it?
- 在哪里啊？
Oh, I don't know, sport.
我也不知道啊
Honey, have you seen the umbrella?
亲爱的 你看见那把伞了吗？
No, can't say that I have.
- 没 没看见
Okay, listen, don't worry about it.
别担心 Mulberry肯定就在附近
I'm sure mrs. Mulberry's around here somewhere.
Or, uh, maybe she's not.
也许不在
She could've left. You know...
说不定走了 也许她去照顾别的小男孩了
maybe she had some other little boy
也许她去照顾别的小男孩了
I don't know. It could be a little boy in,uh...
比如一个在英国的小男孩...
england...
named... spencer.
叫Spencer
I mean, this is conjecture on my part.
我也是瞎猜的
But it is possible that someone like little spencer
但也可能小Spencer更需要Mulberry夫人
needs mrs. Mulberry more, 'cause he doesn't have a daddy
因为他没有疼爱他的爸爸妈妈
and a mommy who love him.
Yeah, that's it.
是呀 他是个孤儿...
He's an orphan...
with no hands.
手也没有
Okay?
你真可爱 我爱你
You're so sweet. Come here. I love you. You all right?
Okay, go get dressed.
穿衣服去吧
What have you done to mrs. Mulberry?
你把Mulberry夫人怎么了？
Until there's a body, there's no evidence of a crime.
没找到“尸体” 就算不上“犯罪”
Mrs. Mulberry!
Mulberry夫人！ 她回来了
She's back!
Mrs. Mulberry's back!
Mulberry夫人回来了
She got ran over. She's dead.
- 她被车压了 她死了
Don't you worry. I'm here.
别担心 有我在
Maybe it's okay, buddy. Maybe we can call 9-1-1 or--
- 没关系 我们可以打911
no, tom, she's gone.
不用了 Tom 她“去”了
swimmers, take your marks.
各就各位 预备
George, what are you doing here?
- George 你来干吗？
Don't worry, Bree, I'll be quick.
- 别担心 Bree 就一会
I thought about what you said, and you're right.
我想了想你说的话 觉得你是对的
Andrew needs his space.
Andrew需要自己的空间 谢谢 George
Well, thank you, George.
谢谢 George 所以我最好退出
It's...best that I stay away.
所以我最好退出
And I completely understand
而且你要换药剂师我也能理解 但是
if you want to change pharmacists but...
I did want to give you a little good-bye gift.
我想送你一件告别礼物
Oh.
噢
It's my pattern! Where did you find it?
- 就是这个图案！你从哪找到的？
I got lucky on an online auction.
网上拍卖碰巧遇到
I love it! Thank you! Oh!
我喜欢！谢谢！
George?
George？
Oh, George!
哦 George！ George
George.
George
Andrew, what are you doing?!
Andrew 你干吗?
Andrew!
Get off of him, Andrew!
给我下来 Andrew!
Stop it!
住手 住手
Knock it off!
住手
Did you see him?! He was kissing her!
- 看见了吗？他竟然亲她！
Oh, my god, you're bleeding.
哦 你流血了
That freak was kissing her!
- 他竟然亲她！
I don't care. You gotta calm down now.
- 不关我事 你得冷静下来
The world is filled with good fathers.
世间好爸爸到处都有
How do we recognize them?
可我们又如何找到他们呢？
They're the ones who are missed so terribly
他们不在身边时 我们会感到绝望崩溃
that everything falls apart in their absence.
They're the ones who love us
他们在孩子还未出生前就深爱着我们
long before we've even arrived.
They're the ones who come looking for us
他们在我们迷失回家的路时还在寻找我们
when we can't find our way home.
hey, what's wrong?
怎么了？
Because of me,
因为我
my son's imaginary friend got crushed by a garbage truck.
儿子的假象朋友被卡车“压死”了
I am the worst person in the world.
我真是世上最差的妈妈
Yes, the world is filled with good fathers...
的确 世间好爸爸到处都有...
honey, he is going to get over this in no time. Trust me.
亲爱的 他很快会忘了这事的 相信我
And one day when he is all grown up,
等有一天Parker长大了
you and Parker are going to laugh hysterically about this.
你们俩会拿这事开玩笑的
You really think so? Really?
真的？
And the best
而最好的父亲 就是那些能让生命中的女人
are the ones who make the women in their lives...
I promise.
我保证
Feel like good mothers.
觉得自己是最好的母亲的人